Hello, I am Abhinash, a CRP who takes
care of his clients. One of those
clients is my client named
Raju. He is 30 years old and
an auto driver here in Raipur. Last month, when
he fell ill, he had to
stay in the hospital for five days for treatment. Due to this illness,
his earnings were stopped for five days. Firstly, there was the
worry of the hospital and then there was the worry of
how he would manage his expenses after leaving the hospital. Then I reminded him
that he had
purchased ICICI Lombard Hotspot On Insurance from me.
He received a
fixed amount from the hospital insurance for five days. Just by providing a
discharge certificate from the hospital and a simple
platform, his claim was settled
and Rs. 2500 for 15 days at the rate of ₹500 per day was credited
to his account.
Not only this, he
can get this for up to 30 days of hospitalization.
Depending on the state, age and his choice,
he had to pay around 262
rupees, in which you can choose the amount from five days to one day, depending on your income and ability to pay.  You
can get protection of Rs 10,000. For your information, keeping
a simple approach in mind,
we have provided you some insurance policies. You
can choose your policy from the following categories as per your convenience and if you have to get
hospitalized, you
can easily get treatment.
Therefore, I suggest that you advise all your
customers to take ICICI Lombard
insurance so that in
case of subscribing to it, they do
not have to worry about losing their earnings because
this insurance gives a fixed amount
per day which enriches their daily earnings
and provides them financial support.
For more information,
click on ICICI Lombard on the CSC portal today and
contact your relationship manager.
Now this is the same thing, neither asafoetida nor alum is used, the
color remains bright. On my suggestion,
Raju bought ICICI Lombard
insurance and secured himself
and your customers should subscribe.
Now
Ajay